Phone

+57 301 3076930

Email

ed.atencio16@gmail.com

Web

edatencio.com

Address

Bogotá, Colombia

# Edward D. Atencio M.

UNITY DEVELOPER / .NET PROGRAMMER

I've worked on a variety of games and programs, including arcade games, console and WinForms apps, and even some Arduino and Node.js projects.

I love nothing more than to mentor other programmers and expand my experience and knowledge as a developer.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Manage a small team of two junior game programmers, an Arduino programmer, and a 3D modeler, supervising their projects, keeping their progress on schedule, giving feedback, and helping out when they get stuck. And also, develop my assigned projects.

Develop video games to be placed in the arcade rooms all around the country, using the Unity game engine and the C# programming language.

Two-month contract done in the IT department, carrying out the support activities in different locations according to the established standards and guidelines.

Two months of academic internships done in the IT department, carrying out the support activities in "Planta Modelo" according to the established standards and guidelines.

#### LEAD PROGRAMMER

Aug 2019 – Jan 2020 Super Videomania, C.A. *Zulia, Venezuela* 

**UNITY DEVELOPER** 

Jul 2018 – Aug 2019 Super Videomania, C.A. *Zulia, Venezuela* 

**IT ANALYST** 

Jul 2017 – Aug 2017 Cervecería Polar C.A. *Zulia, Venezuela* 

#### **ACADEMIC INTERNSHIPS**

Feb 2017 – Mar 2017 Cervecería Polar C.A. *Zulia, Venezuela* 

## **EDUCATION**

COMPUTER SCIENCE BACHELOR'S DEGREE

Zulia, Venezuela

Universidad Rafael Belloso Chacín. Engineering Faculty. Graduated in August of 2017.

CCNA ROUTING & SWITCHING CERTIFICATES

Zulia, Venezuela

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA). Certified in the year 2016.

#### **SKILLS**

Software

C#, C++, JavaScript.

Unity 3D, Visual Studio, Arduino IDE, Node.js, Blender.

Languages

English (advanced), Spanish (native).

Other

- Repairs and maintenance of equipment, both software and hardware.
- Basic knowledge of 3D modeling, rigging, and texturing using Blender.
- Able to assume leadership or to be a team member.